In this video, we'll be defining the term Sampling Distribution,
في هذا الفيديو، سنعرف المصطلح توزيع العينات،
and looking at an example of one specific sampling distribution.
وننظر في أحد أمثلة توزيع العينات المحددة.
A sampling distribution is the distribution of a statistic.
توزيع العينات هو توزيع إحصائية.
This could be any statistic,
يمكن أن يكون ذلك أي إحصائية،
but what does it really mean,
ولكن ماذا يعني ذلك بالفعل،
to look at the distribution of a statistic?
النظر في توزيع إحصائية؟
Consider again the coffee drinking habits of all Udacity students.
فكر مرة أخرى في عادات تناول القهوة لدى جميع طلاب Udacity.
Let's say, each of these cups represents a student,
لنفترض أن كل كوب من هذه الأكواب يمثل طالبًا،
and a green cup represents a student that drinks coffee,
حيث يمثل الكوب الأخضر الطالب الذي يشرب القهوة،
while a red cup represents a student that doesn't drink coffee.
بينما يمثل الكوب الأحمر الطالب الذي لا يشرب القهوة.
And even though there are more students than we represent here,
وعلى الرغم من وجود عدد أكبر من الطلاب مما نمثل هنا،
pretend that this represents all Udacity students.
فلنفترض أن هذا يمثل جميع طلاب Udacity.
If we were to select this group of students to ask about their coffee drinking habits,
إذا كان يجب علينا أن نختار هذه المجموعة من الطلاب لنسألهم عن عادات تناول القهوة لديهم،
what would our population,
فماذا سيكون متوسط السكان
parameter, sample and statistic be?
والمعلمة والعينة والإحصاء؟
Use the quiz below to answer.
استخدم الاختبار التالي للإجابة.
You may want to pause the screen here to return and check your answers.
قد ترغب في إيقاف الشاشة هنا للعودة والتحقق من إجاباتك.